There is a car race near our town every year.
在我们镇子附近每年都有一场汽车比赛.
In 1995, there was a very big race.
1995年举行了一次盛大的比赛.
There were hundreds of people there.
许许多多人都去了赛场.
My wife and I were at the race.
我和我的妻子也去了.
Our friends Julie and Jack were there, too.
我们的朋友Julie和Jack也去了.
You can see us in the crowd.
你可以在人群中看到我们.
We are standing on the left.
我们站在左面.
There were twenty cars in the race.
参加比赛的有20辆汽车.
There were English cars, French cares, German cars.
有英国, 法国, 德国, 意大利,
Italian cars. American cars and Japanese cars.
美国和日本的汽车.
It was an exciting finish.
比赛的结尾是激动人心的.
The winner was Billy Stewart.
获胜者是Billy Stewart.
He was in car number fifteen.
他在第15号车里.
Five other cars were just behind him.
其他5辆汽车紧紧跟在他后面.
On the way home, my wife said to me,
回家的途中, 我妻子对我说,
'Don't drive so quickly!
"别开得这样快!
You're not Billy Stewart!'
你可不是Billy Stewart!"